Hello

My name is Dechen Tshomo,

I have good communication skills. I am creative when working with a team, and good at listening to customers and finding solutions to their needs. I can do social media marketing and page management. I can adapt to any kind of workspace and am used to working under pressure. I have worked as social media manager for a few startups. I am a fast learner and digital enthusiastic. I love meeting new people and learning new things.

Skills

- Good Problem-solving skills
- Social and Digital Enthusiast
- Positive attitude and vibrant personality
- Organizing meetings and event planning
- Good interpersonal skill and highly organized
- Fluency in speaking English
- Creative and innovative

Experience

2011-2016

CLOTH STORE-Bajo town - self employed

- Daily operation of business and sales
- Travelled Nepal, Dakha, and Siliguri, Calcutta to bring in supplies for the store

2017

Edge cafe-Bajo town-self employed

- Daily operation of the business
- Train and support new employee
- Sales and Marketing

2018-2020

Punatshangchu karaoke, Wangdi Phodrang - self-employed

- Page management
- Event management
- Daily operation of business and sales
- To oversee business queries

2020-2021(april)

Druna Ghu cookies & My music Entertainment-Startup centre-Marketing manager

- Page management
- Sales and marketing
- To oversee business queries
- Support and train new employees

Education

2009- Rinchen

2009- Rinchen higher secondary school. 2021(april)-2022-April)- Diploma in Business Managemnt

Awards

Best Idea - (Business Idea Competition) - 2021